KHANH BACH

11000 S. Eastern Ave. #2224, Henderson, NV | (702) 874-8979 | kbach04@hotmail.com

Professional Summary

Result – oriented, efficient and organized Office Manager with 12+ years of experience managing offices and administrative responsibilities in the education and manufacturing industries. Managed administration processes, policies, procedures and responsible for organizing company events such as Christmas and New Year celebration. Facilitated support for employees business travel including hotel accommodations, airfare, travel visas and transportation. Handled new projects within the Human Resources department.

Skills

Control budget Reports preparation Strong planning Strong organizational Filing document **Project Management** Problem Solving Good communication Handle multi-task Manage transportation Team Leadership Ability to prioritize work **Good Negotiation** Good customer service Attention to detail Excellent time management

Experience

Host/Server/Cashier Pho One Restaurant

06/2017 – 05/2019

Lewisville, TX

- Host: welcomed customers with a warm smile and friendly conversation, taking them to their seats and presented them with clean menus in a quick, courteous and professional manner
- Server: deliver exceptional dining experience with deep knowledge of food and fresh ingredients
- To Go Specialists: deliver convenience without compromising quality, taking orders via phone and online system
- Busser: ensured clean dining room and inviting atmosphere for customers
- Cashiering responsibilities

Office Manager Vietnam Gopa Consultant Mbh

01/2016 - 05/2017

Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam

- Take initiative in manager's absence and relieve management of administrative detail, all projects
- Managing the overall office administrative; setting up and maintaining of administrative systems; support functions including the provision of secretarial, cashier and IT support services, general support services to the project
- Responsible to identify, negotiate and manage the service providers to ensure good quality service
- Main support for Hotel booking / transportation coordination/ Visa / Work permit
- Communication with grantees and other stakeholders; sending emails, newsletters; maintaining databases
- Coordinate meetings/workshops, interviews, events and other similar activities

Office Manager

01/2012 – 01/2016

Pepsico International Vietnam

Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam

- Research, evaluate, and recommend office supplies and equipment purchases to minimize costs and meet the organization's business needs.
- Categorize and keep important documents in a proper filing manner
- Co-ordinate with the affiliated companies and legal advisor, if required
- In charge of event or meeting organization for the company or for suppliers which relevant to company business
- Arrange visa, immigration documents and accommodation for visitors/staff relevant to company business
- In collaboration with the HR Manager, develop program of activities that will promote the motivation of the employees
- Organize Board of Director meetings, prepare agenda and minutes and responsible to maintain updated all documentation
- Lead or participate in company assigned projects

Administration Manager Colgate Palmolive Vietnam Ltd

01/2008 - 12/2011

Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam

- Responsible for maximizing efficiency and effectiveness of all general administrative processes such as office administration, communication of business code of conduct and employee code of conduct, office civil works, business licenses, certificates ... to legal papers for expats such as work permits, resident cards, visas, and other related services
- In charge of travel arrangements and negotiate and manage corporate services
- Provide valuable input, initiatives to build key focus AOP yearly and control admin budget
- Organize meetings and events such as Staff Party of over 1,000 attendees, Family Day
- Control annual inventory of office assets and property
- Supports to HR and other functions: implement events/training to promote team-building, EOHS; assist to HR dept about basis of training and development, recruitment, compensation and benefit; others tasks will be assigned in case

Administration Executive Bluescope Steel Vietnam Ltd

01/2005 - 12/2007

Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam

- Liaise with President and VP's to ensure all visits to factory are approved and managed efficiently and safely
- Arrange servicing/repairs of office equipment as appropriate such as printers/ faxes / photocopy machines, order and control the stationery, cartridges, and toners
- Maintain business filing system and manage Canteen Services of the company
- Organization all employee events such as Christmas event, End of New Year event, Zero Harm event, Safety Family Day event, and other events
- Manage coordination of all company cars and owned or hired busses, coordinate with Recruitment Specialist regarding the new starters for transport arrangement, manage pick up points to make sure it safe and manage timing during the route
- Manage all travel and accommodation requirements
- Expiates: manage International assignee visas, and expatriate accommodation, visitors, including short term and long term expiates; coordinate with procurement regarding the leases for renewal of leases expatriate cars

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration

University of Economic

Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam